my glasses never fall out my room my
glass a lot of time really they don't oh
my god are you having a seizure are you
okay why if you go on a roller coaster
Kenan I just went to an amusement park
glasses or contacts contacts glasses
glasses contacts here's the thing abut
have you ever slept with someone yes I
didn't finish my question did you ever
have you ever slept with someone on a
one-night-stand basis that's private yes
but imagine for a second if you had what
are you gonna bring a tiny little bottle
of goobie live literally do every time
every time oh my gosh if it's something
like sight that is so important you're
gonna make sure that you have all the
things you need to make sure you could
put your contacts in the worst part is
when you're intimate with somebody and
they're on top of you this definitely
happened I think we're totally having
sex and I was this close to coming and
his glasses fell on me and then I did
not come for the rest of the week rookie
mistake
take your glasses off before me unless
he had the glasses on he doesn't need to
see people you would have someone with
glasses on you take them off they look
completely different yeah you do not
wanna I don't I read on dating apps that
people who have glasses have 60% chance
of not finding anyone because they were
in class that makes perfect you read
that on dating app yeah they they have
the statistics what kind of adding up
are you on that's telling you no that's
98% of all presidents of course wiped
left because they're just like the
glasses really holding them back there's
only one president I would he
didn't wear glasses are you talking
about Reagan dude no okay
yeah this is 2019 looks matters and I
just want to say that you guys look
crazy
you guys look creatures or losers you
don't have anything to do all day no one
wants to them okay well can you
take your glasses off again
one Wow so much more attractive I can
actually like look at you now and still
beautiful
what glasses on I'm gonna say you feel
really little
I feel like that's bias I I'm sensing
some bias from the side why mmm maybe
because it's convenient for your point I
think every time you take a class that
Sydney wants to you that's what it
seems like
Sydney is it the same for me okay put
the mic on that's fine if she wore those
glasses every day from like since a kid
she would be a virgin nobody wants this
that's not hate it
I'd rather kill myself why did you buy
the big ones that make it look like your
eyes are like two snails squished
together you're right they suck they
suck and think that cuz their glasses
look at me it took them off now I'm a
whole new woman I could anyone I
want I mean let's look at the facts
somebody walks up to you on the street
and like hey can I use your phone and
they're wearing glasses trustworthy I
can trust that guy know somebody would
hopefully Dahmer
Jeffrey Dahmer is someone who wore
glasses and it was not trustworthy and
everyone trusted him and then everyone
found that their dicks were in blue
vases by the end of the year a lot of
people that wear glasses
read books people that read more books
or educators there's a lot of people
reading books who are also pedophiles
folks make you edgy cated and the more
educated you are the less likely you are
to be violent this is statistics it's
crazy that you would say something like
that because you with your glasses on
that shirt you look like every Trader
Joe's employee ever is there something
wrong with being in Trader Joe's
employee the best people I know we're
contacts Denzel Washington Halle Berry
Angelina Jolie she must lady gaga what
about guys Jesus wore contacts you know
that is not true Jesus is not real for
sure probably he probably had some sort
of magical contact way to see instead
there's no way he well maybe that's why
the Jews killed I'm sure everybody know
I'm Jewish
um I am too
have you ever had your limbs fall into
your eye and then cured heart cut your I
know and then you don't have an eye and
then you take your eye out does it look
like either of us have had that happen
to know she's saying that it could it
could happen never heard of that seven
sisters fiance who she was going to
marry but the shards went into his eye
and so that he became blind and she
didn't marry him like imagine if you get
in a car accident and you have your
glasses on the glass and your leg the
lens you can go into your eye and then
you're blind forever but your contacts
can flip up into the back of your eye
and you need to lift your eye lit up and
you need to put somebody the first thing
they're gonna do is to knock your
glasses off you'll be gone first thing
not everybody can not get in a fight
boom yeah they come off so easy what if
I'm doing this what are you gonna do
sword what about a sword and I'm
attacking you like this what are you
gonna do you can't even don't you gonna
you gonna take them out when you get
knocked out in a fight you're gonna die
it up hold on and take them out before
you have to take your glasses off when
you get in a fight yeah you have to look
across everything and say let me take my
glasses off and then you have to tell
your mother to hold your glasses for you
you don't need takes a second one you
have a case I don't have you ever seen
anyone do something like this you know
what needs cases you know in these cases
that's I've seen the movie all yours to
eat it out or eat it up eat it ya lap up
what it be able to say my glasses never
follow up i roll my glass out of time
really they don't all office
oh my are you having a seizure are you
okay I'm I'm giving you an example what
if you what if you go on a roller
coaster
I just went to an amusement park
I just watched a movie you didn't have
to go to a waterpark
same yeah you definitely can't wear
glasses I've worn my glasses
you can freefall yeah Oh mine completely
intact this is so glasses of you you can
go skydiving with glasses on yeah you're
like I wouldn't I wouldn't do it if
you're in the shower and it fogs up your
glasses definitely so you have to take
your glasses off just to wash your body
that sounds so tragic I feel sorry for
you I don't know about you but I don't
really need to see that much when I'm
taking a shower
oh so that means you don't clean
properly there's a whole bunch of
crevices or it means you don't like your
body yeah you got if you have if you
have a penis you have to look at it and
wash all areas of it you got to flip it
and then you got to look at the scrotum
and you got to flip the baby maybe I'm
just in tune with my body and I know
where everything is since I've been
living in it for a couple of years now
yeah and I know where the Washington and
what to do right
sorry he understands crumbs better than
you do you did because you don't put
scrotums in your mouth so you have no
idea but women know and that's what
we're telling you you don't watch them
properly and that's why people do I
don't wear them in the shower and we
know that they're not cleaning properly
that's all it is last time mr. scrotum I
was like oh this is a must wear glasses
I look up uh-huh glasses for you in the
shower I put in my contacts so that when
I'm in the shower I can spend at least
three minutes looking at my beautiful
body and thanking it for being such a
you got a check for moles so you got a
check for like discoloration there could
be lumps like you need to see it's a
health hazard scrotums disgusting me you
know what you Ava
yeah cuz cuz you I'm not going here
telling you like yeah like do i
jaywalkers squeezing the
hares is grooming thing and and watch
better is high your scrotum is nasty cuz
you don't get in there right I get in
there fine okay wrinkles and you just
rub it down like it's a window both of
you take off your gossip book look and
see how dirty they are so literally you
know I cleaned it right here oh you're
dirty filthy shirt and it still looks
who raised you you have no manners who
cleans their glasses could you clean
your fingers with your shirt oh these
look like a constellation disgusting I
think he's an outlier okay listen up I
I've had enough we're out the last five
to ten minutes
you guys have constantly been berating
me about the way I look with glasses the
way I look without glasses and now
you're talking about how clean my
scrotum is like it's gone too far
I don't with this I don't find this
sick and honestly Ava I'm over it so
good conversation you're just what I'm
doing yeah didn't see that there is
nothing you wouldn't be able to walk out
you guys he has a hygiene problem
he might have hygiene problem my glasses
are still more convenient it's weird
that you wouldn't stick with your
glasses buddy you just did you want me
to lead to I mean whatever I was talking
about your scrotum to I want to inspect
the back of your ears
we're bullies but at least we're hot can
you come here Mike soon come back
we could do we could do anything with
good dance yeah we won that's oh so hard
so great we're awesome
I do wear glasses at night though